<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>WaSkeleton</modNameReadable>
    <linkUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2159119022</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>WaSkeleton_1_0_3_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.3.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>The mod now has some added features. In the options for the mod it is now possible to turn of the death-explosion for those who want to.

There is also an option to enable reanimation of dead pawns! Dead pawns that have rotted to the point of being just a skeleton can reanimate as a skeleton pawn during the night, provided they are not missing some vital bodypart. 
You can select to only reanimate dead colonists as well as restrict it only to buried pawns.

I hope you will like this addition and if you have any ideas for more features, please leave a comment on the mod page or on the linked Discord-server!
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>WaSkeleton_1_0_6_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.6.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>There is now an option to add the ressurected Hediff to all skeletons, not just those ressurected during the game but also all guests, starting pawns and others.
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>WaSkeleton_1_0_19_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.19.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>img:Zombie|caption:There is now an option for adding zombies to the game. These will rarely spawn for a corpse during the rot-stage and their minds are more fuzzy and they are therefor immune to psychic fenomena. 
They are however hideous to look at and because of their limited mental abilities will perform tasks even slower than the skeletons.|
Activate it in the mod-options if it sounds interresting and thanks to NonSpecific for the textures!

Fixed in this version is that skeleton and zombies do not feel pain. This was always intended and should now be working.</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>WaSkeleton_1_0_24_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>1.0.24.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>This update adds the option to ressurect only during eclipses, by request.

It also adds an option to ressurect all valid corpses at once, for you who want a large skeleton-raid four days after that tribal faction assulted your colony, all because you forgot to burn the corpses in time :)
</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
	<HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="WaSkeleton_UpdateFeatureBase">
		<defName>WaSkeleton_1_4_3</defName>
		<assemblyVersion>1.4.3</assemblyVersion>
		<content>Due to a bad interaction with the developer of the HAR framework combined with the increased work required I have decided to not further update this mod. It will stay up to support the previous versions of the game.</content>
	</HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>
</Defs>
